<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Icon Pusher</string>
    <string name="send_title">Submit Apps</string>
    <string name="send_data">Submit apps to add them to the icon request list.</string>
    <string name="info_title">Information</string>
    <string name="info_data">Submit your installed applications then view on iconpusher.com to get details needed for icon pack development</string>
    <string name="privacy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_data_1">Icon Pusher is built and maintained by southpaw.dev, any questions can be sent to hello@southpaw.dev.</string>
    <string name="privacy_data_2">Icon Pusher scans the installed apps on your phone and collects the package names, activity names and icons of the selected applications. The package and activity names are just what the developer chose when creating the app, no personal information is collected by Icon Pusher. The only other piece of information the app accesses is the unique device ID. The unique device ID is a randomly generated hexidecimal value which contains no personal information and can not be used to gain information about you or your device.</string>
    <string name="privacy_data_3">The unique device ID and the package names, collection names and icons of the selected apps are then sent to the iconpusher.com website. The unique device ID is only used by the site to filter the app list to just the apps which were sent by the device.</string>
    <string name="privacy_data_4">The website iconpusher.com lists the historical package and activity names of packages to be used by icon pack developers. The app details (package names, activity names &amp; icons) sent to the website will be publicly available but there will not be any means to link the apps to you.</string>

    <string name="action_about">About</string>


    <string name="submit_icon">Submit Icon</string>
    <string name="cancel">Close</string>
    <string name="upload_button_description">Send package details to the iconpusher.com website</string>
    <string name="select_all">Select All</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>

</resources>